Interviewer: Who do you look like in your family?
Lewis: Er, well people say I often look like my dad a lot.
We’ve got the same sort of nose and the same face shape,
but I’ve got my mum’s hair colour and my mum’s eyes.
Interviewer: Do you have a similar personality?
Lewis: Er, again there is, there are quite a lot of similarities between me and my dad.
We’re both into German and speaking German,
and also into architecture, which is why I’m here.
Interviewer: Do you have a favourite painting?
Susie: Um, I think so.
I’m not sure of the name of the painting, but I like Salvador Dalí.
I really like the painting with the dripping clocks.
Interviewer: Can you describe it?
Susie: Er, yes, like I said, there are dripping clocks.
It’s very, um, it’s an interesting style.
It’s not something you see all the time, and it’s very colourful.
Interviewer: Where did you go for your last holiday?
Shosanna: My last vacation I went to Guyana,
which is my parents’ country in South America.
Interviewer: Did you have a good time?
Shosanna: I did. It was actually one of the best vacations I had.
It was really educational, and I was able to see how my parents grew up, which was interesting.
Interviewer: Do you take a lot of photos?
Susan: I take a lot of photos.
My telephone is full of photos and I use Instagram.
Interviewer: What do you usually take photos of?
Susan: Mostly people, places, gardens, lots of flowers.
I never post photos of people, but I take photos of family,
but lots of gardens and flowers.
Interviewer: Do you prefer films with a happy or sad ending?
Sam: Um, it just has to be a good film.
I don’t mind if it’s a happy ending or a sad ending.